- 안녕
- 안녕, 잠깐 기다려
Hold on a second.
Nice.
잘했어!
I got you something.
너한테 줄 게 있어
What's this?
- 이게 뭔데?
- 812달러야
Eight hundred and twelve bucks.
Didn't Big Leon tell you?
It's a thousand...
누가 값을 불렀는지 몰라도
날 밤새 원한다면 천 달러야
...to have me for the whole night.
What's this for?
왜 주는데?
Well, I'm making money now.
돈이 좀 생겨서
그 동안 밀린 전기세며
얻어먹은 피자 값이야
I'm paying you back for headshots,
electric bills, all that pizza....
I love you, man.
- 정말 고마웠어
- 잘 받을게
Well, thanks, man.
Now I can get my pony.
이걸로 조랑말도 사겠다
This is a little extra something for...
또 있어, 이건 내가
하고 싶었던 거야
...always being there for me.
Wow, I don't know what to say.
뭐라고 해야 될지 모르겠다
What do you say?
- 어때?
- 몰라!
I don't know.
It's a bracelet.
- 팔찌네
- 그래, 뭐라고 새겼는지 봐
Isn't it? It's engraved, too.
Check it out.
"To my best bud."
'최고의 벗에게'
Thanks, best bud.
고마워, 최고의 벗
Put it on.
- 차 봐!
- 지금?
Now?
No, it should be saved
for a special occasion.
아냐, 이런 건 아꼈다가
특별한 날에만 차야지
아냐, 이건 액세서리야
어디든 잘 어울린다고
No, that's the beauty part.
It goes with everything.
이걸 차면
잘나가 보일걸?
When you put this on,
you're good to go.
Oh, man!
멋진데
너한테 참 잘 어울린다
You are so wearing that bracelet!
I so am!
그렇구나
Any idea what this will
do for your sex life?
이걸 차면 네 성생활이
돌변할걸?
처음엔 이거 푸는 데
시간이 좀 걸리겠지만
It might slow down at first, but...
익숙해지면 다시 똑같을걸
...once I'm used to the extra weight,
I'll be back on track.
The One With the Prom Video
-This all looks good.
-Great.
- 이력서는 훌륭하군요
- 고맙습니다
If I want to call for a reference
on your last job...?
가장 최근에 한 일이 뭐죠?
챈들러 빙 씨의
매니저였어요
That's right there, see?
The manager, Chandler Bing?
All right.
그럼 실력을 직접 보죠
샐러드를 만들어 봐요
Let's see if you're as good in person
as you are on paper. Make me a salad.
A salad? I could do
something more complicated.
더 어려운 것도
할 수 있는데요
샐러드면 충분해요
No, just the salad will be fine.
알겠어요
You got it.
Now I want you to tell me what
you're doing while you're doing it.
요리를 하는 동안
과정을 설명해 봐요
좋아요
양상치부터 뜯겠습니다
All right. Well,
I'm tearing the lettuce.
Is it dirty?
- 더러운가요?
- 걱정 마세요, 씻을 거예요
Oh, I'm gonna wash it.
아뇨, 난 더러운 게 좋아요
Don't. I like it dirty.
그럼 그렇게 하죠
That's your call.
So, what are you going to do next?
그 다음에는 뭘 하죠?
I thought that l'd
cut up the tomatoes.
토마토를 썰려고 하는데요
Are they firm?
단단한가요?
They're okay.
싱싱해요
You sure they haven't gone bad?
썩지는 않았는지 확인했나요?
You sure they're not very, very bad?
설마 푹 썩지는 않았겠죠?
괜찮다니까요
No, really, they're okay.
가로로 자를 겁니까?
You gonna slice them up real nice?
채를 썰 건데요
I was going to do them julienne.
I'm out of here!
그만두겠어요!
Hello?
여보세요
Rachel's not here.
Can I take a message?
레이첼이 없는데
메모 남기실래요?
How do we spell Casey?
케이시? 만화 주인공이요?
아님 가수 케이시요?
Is it like "at the bat"
or "and The Sunshine Band"?
그래요, 안녕
Hey, who's this Casey?
- 대체 케이시가 누구야?
- 극장에서 만난 남자래
A guy she met at the movies.
왜 전화한 거지?
What does he want with her?
춤추자고 꼬시겠지
I guess he wants to
do a little dance...
...you know, make a little love....
그러다 애정표현도 좀 하고
Well, get down tonight.
오늘 만리장성 쌓자는 거지
I don't know. I don't
정말 이해가 안 돼
두 달 전만 해도 레이첼과 난
이렇게 가까웠다구
I don't get it! Two months ago,
Rachel and I were this close.
한데 지금은 다른 남자 전화나
받고 있다니
Now I'm taking messages from guys
she meets at the movies?
I mean, this Casey should be
taking down my messages, you know?
이 케이시란 남자가
내 전화를 받고 있어야지
아님 나랑 둘이
전화 응답기를 같이 사든지
Or Rachel and I should be together...
...and we should get
some kind of message service.
Hang in there.
It's gonna happen.
좀 기다려 봐
꼭 그렇게 될 거야
어떻게 알아?
Now, how do you know that?
Because she's your lobster.
레이첼은 네 바닷가재니까
Oh, she's going somewhere.
또 시작이군
It's a known fact that lobsters
fall in love and mate for life.
바닷가재는 한 번
사랑에 빠지면 평생 간대
You know what? You can actually
see old lobster couples...
오래된 커플은 둘이
집게를 마주잡고 걸어다닌대
...walking around their tank,
holding claws, like....
Hey, you feeling better?
기분 좀 나아졌어?
Yeah, I think that fifth shower
got the interview off me.
샤워를 네 번 하고 나니까
그 인터뷰 생각이 사라졌어
Do you have other possibilities?
다른 방도는 없겠어?
There is the possibility
that I won't make rent.
방세를 안 내는 방도가 있지
그렇게 급하면 내가 꿔줄게
If you want,
I can lend you money.
아냐, 그랬다가 못 갚으면
오빠 볼 면목이 없잖아
If I couldn't pay you back right away,
I'd feel guilty and tense around you.
그럼 부모님께 말씀드려
Then why not borrow it
from Mom and Dad?
You feel guilty and tense
around them already.
어차피 죄책감 같은 건
잊은 지 오래잖아
떼어먹어도 되고
Might as well
make some money off of them.
The man's got a point.
정곡을 찌르다니
What is that sparkly thing?
그 번쩍거리는 게 뭐야?
그게...
That thing?
Yeah, it's a little flashy.
좀 요란하긴 하지?
No, no.
아니, 절대 아냐
No, no. It's not flashy.
Not for a goodfella.
'최고의 벗'이라면
이 정도는 차 줘야지
훌륭한걸?
돈도 꽤 줬겠어
Man, that is sharp! That must
have cost you quite a few doubloons.
- 안녕, 얘야
- 오셨어요?
Hi, darling.
What's this?
- 이게 뭐예요?
- 오래된 네 물건이란다
Some of your old stuff.
Well, sweetie,
we have a surprise for you.
깜짝 놀랄 소식이 있다
네 방을 체육관으로
개조할 거야
We're turning your room into a gym.
Wow, that is a surprise!
정말 놀랄 만하네요
Just one question.
Why not Ross's room?
한데 왜 오빠 방이 아니죠?
그 생각도 했는데 네 오빠는
트로피며 배지가 너무 많잖니
We talked about that...
... but your brother had so many
science trophies, plaques, merit badges....
We didn't want to disturb them.
- 그걸 치워버릴 순 없잖니
- 신도 노하실걸요
God forbid!
- 오랜만이다, 레이첼
- 안녕하세요
We were so sorry to hear
about your parents splitting up.
부모님 일은 정말 유감이다
그냥 별거 중이신데요 뭐
두고 봐야죠
Well, they're just separated.
You never know! We'll see.
I can't say any of us
were surprised.
실은 예상하던 일이란다
They've been unhappy
ever since we've known them.
아주 불행한 커플이었거든
Especially after
that incident in Hawaii.
특히 그 하와이 사건
이후로는 더 그랬지
What? What incident?
무슨 사건이요?
내가 착각한 건가?
내 얘기일지도 몰라
No, no. I must be
thinking of someone else.
Maybe me!
지금 바쁘지 않니?
어서 가서 빨래 정리해
Don't you have some folding to do?
Fold. You fold.
- 더 줄까?
- 아니, 됐어
-Want a refill?
-I'm all right, thanks.
잠깐, 제대로 한번 해볼게
Give me a second.
I want to get this just right.
이봐, 네 뒤에
죽이는 여자 좀 봐
Dude, eleven o'clock,
totally hot babe checking you out.
나 잘했지?
이제 물건만 있음 남자야
That was really good.
I think I'm ready for my penis now.
I know what you're thinking.
Dave Thomas, founder of Wendy's.
무슨 생각하시는지 압니다
TV 광고에서 많이 본 듯하죠?
I'm Gail.
- 전 게일이에요
- 챈들러입니다
미안하지만 갑자기
일이 생겨서, 반가웠어요
I really have to go,
but it was nice meeting you.
뭐...?
Excellent!
너무해! 비디오나 골프채도
줄 수 있는데 왜 하필이면
He could have gotten me a VCR
or a set of golf clubs.
여자들이 치를 떠는 금팔찌야?
But no! He got me
the "woman repeller"!
이런 걸 대체 어디서 샀을까?
The eyesore from
the Liberace House of Crap!
-It's not bad.
-Easy for you to say.
봐 줄 만해
그런 말은 누가 못해
네가 직접 찬다고 생각해 봐!
You're not sporting a reject
from the Mr. Tcollection!
챈들러...
"l pity the fool that
puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!"
진짜야! 이걸 만든 사람도
아마 비웃을걸?
"l pity that fool"
그걸 차다니!
어서 와!
Hey, man! We were just
doing some impressions.
연기연습 중이었어
너도 원숭이 흉내 내봐
Do your Marcel Marceau.
That's actually good.
똑같다
Would you look at that guy?
저 남자 좀 봐
언제까지 떠들 셈이지?
How long has he
been talking to her?
레이첼은 웨이트리스지
접대부가 아니라구!
It's like, back off, buddy!
She's a waitress, not a geisha.
I think she's okay.
레이첼은 좋아하는데?
Look at that!
저것 봐!
She pushes him away
and he won't budge!
레이첼이 미는데도
안 가잖아
I'm gonna do something.
가서 쫓아내야겠어
산장을 하나 구해서
스키도 타러 갑시다
We'll get a condo...
... right on the mountain.
Ski in, ski out, it's great.
재밌겠네요
Excuse me? Are you Rachel?
실례지만
레이첼 씨인가요?
What?
뭐?
제가 로스 겔러입니다
Ross Geller.
God, in your ad you said
you were pretty, but wow!
광고에는 예쁘다고
써 놨는데 영...
What are you doing?
무슨 짓이야?
오늘이 아니던가요?
Oh, my God, is this the wrong day?
우리가 잘된다면
이것도 추억이 되겠네요
I don't believe it!
If it works out, we'll have
something to tell the grandkids!
You sure will.
그러시겠네요
전 그럼 이만...
I've gotta go.
- 그럼 안녕히
- 만나서 반가웠소
Take care.
See you later.
You're welcome.
괜찮아
-What?
-I was saving you.
뭐가?
내가 구해 줬잖아
Saving me from a pleasant
conversation with an interesting man?
괜찮은 남자랑 기분 좋게
대화하는데 구해 줬다고?
내 자리에서 봤을 땐...
From where I was
Okay, Ross, listen to me.
내 말 잘 들어
날 구해 줄 필요 없어
I am not yours to save.
But you are.
- 필요 있어
- 뭐?
What?
넌 내 바닷가재인걸
You're my lobster.
지금 발작할 시간이야?
Are you being
the blind-date guy again?
No, you're my lobster.
넌 내 바닷가재야
들어 봐, 바닷가재들은
그러니까 같은 물에서...
Lobsters....
In the tank, when they're old...
...they get with the
They walk around holding the claws.
오래도록 같이 사는데
집게를 잡고 걷거든
둘이 서로 부둥켜안고
같은 물에서...
In the tank!
You know, with...
...with the holding and....
Pheebs, you wanna help me
with the lobster thing?
피비, 네가 좀 해봐
Do the claws again.
집게 모양을 해야지
Rach, forget the lobsters, okay?
가재 얘긴 그만두고
우리 얘기 좀 해
Let's talk
What about us?
Ross, there is no "us," okay?
맘대로 우리란 말 쓰지 마
- 하지만...
- 아냐, 내 말 잘 들어
No! Listen to me!
I fell for you and I get clobbered.
내가 너한테 빠졌다가
한 방 먹었지
You then fall for me
and I again get clobbered.
너도 나한테 빠졌다
한 방 먹었고
I'm tired of being
clobbered, you know?
이젠 정말 지겨워
더 이상 그럴 가치가 없다구
It's just not worth it.
Well, but
- 하지만...
- 그만 해!
No "but," Ross.
We are never gonna happen, okay?
Accept that.
우린 절대로 안 돼
그걸 받아들여
누굴 받아들이라고?
Except that what?
No. No.
아니...
Accept that.
끝난 걸 인정하라구
Hey, man! Look, it's my best bud!
How you doing?
내 최고의 벗 왔구나
잘 다녀왔어?
너 정말 원숭이랑 똑같더라
You're getting good at that
Marcel Marceau thing.
이건 어때? 공놀이하자
What do you say we play some ball?
You and me, huh?
Okay, that's my bad.
괜찮아, 내 거니까
If you hated the bracelet,
you should have just said so.
팔찌가 그렇게 싫었으면
말을 했으면 될 거 아냐?
Doesn't the fact that I wore it...
싫어도 하고 다닌 걸 보면
...say how much
our friendship means to me?
내가 얼마나 우리의 우정을
소중하게 여기는지 알겠지?
네가 그렇게 큰소리로
나와 팔찌를 비웃은 건?
But you insulted the bracelet
and you made fun of me.
Well, that's the part
where I'm a wank.
그건 잘못한 거지만
I was hoping you
wouldn't focus on that.
그냥 넘어가 주길 바랬어
야, 미안하단 말을
수백 번은 더 했다
Come on, man! I said I was
sorry a hundred times.
다시는 내 손목에서
풀지 않을게, 약속해
I promise, I will never
take it off my...
...wrist.
그래도 그 안에 있겠다면
계속 있든지
But if you want to
stay in there and be mad...
...you just, you stay in there.
You know what the
넌...
I am here, on my knees...
무릎까지 꿇었어
이 소파쿠션을 내 슬픔과
후회의 상징으로서 들고
... holding up these couch cushions...
...as a symbol
of my sorrow and regret.
Much like they did
in biblical times.
성경에도 나오듯이
'아직도 분노를
금치 못하시겠다면... '
Though you may haveth anger now....
스태피 그래프
몸매 죽이는데?
You know, that Steffi Graf
has quite a tush.
보이는 대로 말했을 뿐이야
I'm just saying!
It's right there!
Hey, guys.
- 오셨어요?
- 그래
Hi, darling.
You didn't bring my grandson?
우리 손자는 안 데려왔니?
He's at Carol and Susan's today.
캐롤과 수잔 집에 있어요
A woman in my office is a lesbian.
우리 사무실에도
레즈비언이 있단다
그냥 그렇다고
I'm just saying!
Jack, look! There's that house
paint commercial that cracks you up!
당신이 좋아하는
페인트 광고가 나왔네요
- 어디 갔었어?
- 상심에 빠져 있었지
-Where have you been?
-Emotional hell.
Did they lend you the money?
아직 돈 얘기 못 드렸어?
- 말도 못 꺼냈어
- 모니카, 말해
No, I haven't asked them yet.
Come on, Monica, do it.
Hey, you guys.
저기요...
모니카가 할말이 있대요
Monica has some news.
진작 말씀드리려고 했는데
실은...
So listen, I'm sorry I didn't
tell you this before, but...
... I'm no longer at my job.
I had to leave it.
저 직장 그만뒀어요
Why?
왜?
그만두라고 하니까요
Because they made me.
You were fired?
What are you gonna do?
해고됐다고?
어쩌면 좋아
Judy, relax. This is our little
Harmonica we're talking about.
여보, 진정해
얘는 우리 딸 모니카야
We taught her well.
우리가 잘 가르쳤잖아
월급의 10%는 어떻게 하랬지?
-Ten percent of your paycheck goes?
-ln the bank.
- 저축하랬죠
- 저축이요
So she dips into her savings.
That's what it's there for.
거봐, 저축한 걸 쓰면 돼
얘는 끄떡없을 거라구
She's gonna be fine.
혹시라도 도움이 필요하면
여기서 찾아보렴
If you need a little extra...
...you know where to find it.
Anything larger back there?
더 큰돈은 없나요?
믿을 수가 없어
I can't believe it!
Would you stop already?
아직도 그 소리야?
이제 그만 좀 잊어버려
Get out of the bitter barn
and play in the hay.
그래, 지금부터 잊어 주지
Oh, you're right.
I should play in the hay.
I just dropped $400 to replace
a bracelet I hated to begin with.
끔찍하게 싫은 팔찌를 사려고
400달러나 쓴 사실을 말야
Bring on the hay!
이제 완전히 잊었어!
Hey!
야!
이거 보면 놀랄걸?
건터가 뭘 찾았게?
I've got something
that'll make you happy.
Guess what Gunther found?
그럼 이제 두 개네!
Hey, now you have two!
그럼 이제 두 개네...
Oh, now you have two.
What am I gonna do?
이제 어떡하지?
이봐!
왔어?
How come you have two?
왜 두 개나 돼?
하난 네 거야
This one's for you.
Get out!
- 말도 안 돼!
- 나도 알아
No, I can't.
이게 너한테 얼마나
소중한지 알아
I know how much this means to you...
그냥 팔찌가 아니라 우리가
'최고의 벗'이란 뜻이잖아
...and this is about more than jewelry.
It's about you and me
and the fact that we're "best buds."
Is this friendship?
I think so!
- 우정의 징표라고?
- 그래!
우린 팔찌로 뭉친 친구야
Check it out!
We're bracelet buddies!
너무 정감 있는 표현 아니니?
That's what they'll call us!
Okay, here you go.
Pay me back whenever you like.
네가 좋을 때 갚아
공룡 그림 수표네
You have dinosaur checks?
그래, 돈으로도 쓰고
공룡도 보고...
You get your money
and you learn something.
What's wrong with that?
- 뭐 불만 있어?
- 아냐
Nothing.
너 참 싸구려 공룡이구나!
Hey, you're a cheap-a-saurus!
농담이야
정말 고마워
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Thank you, I'm very grateful.
모니카, 이게 뭐야?
Hey, Mon, what is this?
고교 때 입던 수영복이야
That's my bathing suit from high school.
I was a little bigger then.
살이 좀 쪘었지
I thought they used that
to cover Connecticut when it rains.
코네티컷에 폭우가 쏟아지면
이걸로 막으면 되겠다
Hey, what's on this videotape?
이 비디오 테입은 뭐지?
몰라, 틀어 보자
I don't know.
Let's put it in.
- 안녕
여기요
됐어요, 잭
Over here, Jack. Okay.
Rachel's coming up the path.
레이첼이 파란 색으로
치장했네, 너무 예쁘죠?
Doesn't she look pretty? Jack?
Can you get this?
세상에!
Oh, my God!
코가 왜 저래?
What is with your nose?
조금 튀어나온 부분이 있어서
깎았어
They had to reduce it
because of my deviated septum.
Okay, I was wrong. That's
what they use to cover Connecticut.
아까 한 말 취소야
저거야 말로 코네티컷을
가리고도 남겠다
이거 우리가 졸업파티
가기 전에 찍은 거야
This is us getting ready
for the prom.
아니, 이건 볼 필요 없어
We don't have to watch.
- 아냐, 볼래
- 재미있잖아
Yeah, we do.
-Come on!
-It's fun!
Get a shot of Monica.
모니카도 찍었어요?
얘는 어디 있는 거야
Where's Monica?
Over here, Dad!
여기 있어요
Wait. How do you zoom out?
화면에 다 안 들어가네
이제 됐다
There she is!
어떤 애가 모니카를 삼켰어!
Some girl ate Monica!
Shut up!
The camera adds ten pounds.
원래 카메라로 찍으면
5킬로는 더 쪄 보여
저건 카메라 몇 대를 쓴 거야?
So how many cameras
are actually on you?
Oh, you look so great!
너 정말 예쁘다!
So do you! You look beautiful!
너도야, 예뻐!
-Oops.
- What?
- 어머나
- 왜?
I think I got mayonnaise on you.
마요네즈 묻었어
괜찮아, 옷도 아니고
겨우 어깬데 뭘
Oh, it's just the shoulder,
not my dress.
모두 웃어 봐
Everybody smile!
- 아빠, 찍지 말아요!
- 안 찍어
Oh, Dad, turn it off!
It is off.
거짓말 말아요
그럼 빨간 불은 뭐예요?
It is not!
What's with the red light?
꺼졌단 말이야
It's the off light.
로스!
Right, Ross?
멋진데? 콧수염 씨
Looking good, Mr. IKotter.
- 너 오늘 정말 예쁘다
- 고마워
- You look pretty tonight.
-Oh, thanks.
여름엔 뭐 할 거야?
- What are you doing this summer?
-I'm gonna hang out...
뭐 그냥...
음악 작업이나 하면서
... work on my music.
후크가 열렸어?
왜 자꾸 흘러내리지?
Is my hook unhooked?
These things keep falling down.
글쎄 모르겠다...
Let me see. I don't know.
What are you gonna do...
- 넌 뭐 할 건데?
- 남자애들 왔다!
The guys are here!
... this summer?
이번 여름에...
음악 작업을 해?
Work on your music?
로이 거블릭이야
Oh, my God!
There's Roy Gublik!
스타워즈를 317번이나 봤대
그래서 신문에도 났었지
You know, Roy saw
Star Wars 317 times.
He was in the paper.
Where's Chip?
Why isn't he here yet?
왜 칩스는 안 오지?
He'll be here, okay?
Take a chill pill.
올 거야
수선떨지 마, 됐지?
There.
로이가 가슴을 만졌다고
말하는 거야
I just told Rachel
that Roy touched my boob.
I can't go to the prom without a date.
I can't! It's too late!
파트너도 없이 어떻게
파티에 가? 이젠 틀렸어
네가 안 가면 나도 안 가
If you're not going,
then I don't want to go.
Oh, I'm gonna kick Chip's ass!
칩스 녀석 오기만 해봐!
네가 레이첼과 같이 가면
어떻겠니?
I have a wonderful idea.
You should take Rachel to the prom.
내가 어떻게...
Doubtful.
당신이 좀 얘기해 봐요
Jack, give me that.
Talk to your son.
- 그래, 자
- 꽤 무겁네
All right, go on.
This thing's heavy.
Your mother's right.
Take her. You can wear my tux.
네 엄마 말이 맞다
같이 가
내 턱시도 빌려 줄게
She won't wanna go with me.
- 레이첼이 싫어할 거예요
- 대학생 오빠인데 왜...
Of course she would!
You're a college man!
- 그래도요
- 한번 시도해 봐
-I don't know.
- Well, come on.
Don't you wanna find out?
졸업파티에도 못 가다니
어떻게 이런 일이...
I can't believe
I can't go to the prom!
This is so harsh!
- 좋아요, 이거 부탁해요
- 장하다, 내 아들!
-Hold my board.
- Thataboy! Thataboy!
볼 거 다 봤지?
이제 끄자
I think we've seen enough.
Let's turn it off.
안 돼! 더 보고 싶어!
그럼 난 안 볼 거야
Well, I'm not gonna watch.
자, 서둘러
Come on, kid. Let's go!
- 잘 어울리는데?
- 내려가자
-My! Are you handsome!
-Let's show them!
Just a sec, Dad.
잠깐만요
Okay, be cool. Just be cool.
침착해, 넌 할 수 있어
Okay, Dad.
- 가요, 아버지
- 레이첼, 멋진 네 기사가 온다
Rachel, ready or not,
here comes your knight in shining
저런!
Oh, no.
- 안녕히 계세요
- 다녀올게요
Don't wait up!
- 먼저 주무세요
- 가자, 칩스!
Chip!
Oh, dear!
이걸 어째...
잭, 이거 어떻게 끄죠?
How do I turn this off?
Press the button.
- 버튼을 눌러
- 어느 버튼요?
Which one? Which button? Jack!
그 버튼!
The button! The button!
I can't believe you did that.
오빠가 저랬는지 몰랐어
Yeah, well....
그래
봤지? 한 쌍의 가재라니까
See? He's her lobster!
Dance with him!
아빠랑 춤춰라
Mom, I'm hungry!
엄마, 또 배고파요
Dance with your father.
아빠랑 춤춰 봐
요즘 춤은 잘 모르지만
나도 한때 날렸다구
I don't know any of your flashdances,
but I'm no slouch on the dance floor.
All right.
-Oh, Jack!
-Oh, Judy!
- 오, 잭!
- 오, 쥬디!